Guide to the Martha Wilson Papers, 1950-2021 (bulk 1964-2006) MSS.175
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Subject Files, 1960-2011; 3 DVDs; 700 Megabytes in one computer disc.
  - Subseries A: Art and Personal Files
    - Censorship [Comm.] (2/2), 1989-1996 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Chelsea Deal 97, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - College of Fine Arts, Arizona State University, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Consulting and Perf research 2002. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Contemporarea Nancy Reagan Oct. 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Cooper Union brochure, 1994 w/ Tipper Gore (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Copyright, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Corcoran, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Courts, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1974-75 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Creative Artist Public Services Programs (CAPS) and Grants, 1975-1976 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1975-1980 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1977-1978 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, 1978-1982 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Creative Artists Public Services Program (CAPS) and Grants, Undated (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Current Biz 6/97-, 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - DCA Artist Certification, 1995 (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Develop Don't Destroy Brooklyn, 2005-2008 (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Diary Stuff from Houseboat, Undated (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Dick Higgins, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Disband Songs, 1978-1982, undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Documenta Archiv, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Dr. Rafael Montanez Ortiz, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Encyclopedia Americana (contains disc), 1998 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - English, General, Mar. 22, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - envelope labeled Barbara Kirschenblatt-Gimblett articles and papers, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Exalicers, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Exercise, undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Fales Library Dinner April 12, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Father - Daughter, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Feminist Art Resource, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Fernando's ID, ca 1985 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Film as Art (1/2), 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Film as Art (2/2), 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - FOTB, 1987-88 working notes, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - FOTB (The Book Book), 1992 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - FOTB travel, 1987, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Gellerman, Hope, 1982-1986 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - General Conceptual, 1970,1972,1975 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - GS, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (1/5), 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (2/5), 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (3/5), 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (4/5) (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Gigs 1988-1991 (5/5) (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Gimblett, Max - Envelope, Undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Gloria - Sept. 13 - Oct. 20, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Going Virtual course description - NYU, Spring 2000 (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Gomez, Edward - Fulbright Grant Reference Form, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Grantmakers and Avocus articles, 1993-1995 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Graphoanalysis (1/5), 1974-1977 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Graphoanalysis (2/5), 1974-1977 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Graphoanalysis (3/5), 1974-1977 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Graphoanalysis (4/5), Undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Graphoanalysis (5/5), Undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Green Folder (1/8); Nancy Reagan b/w [Marilyn Zimmara], undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Green Folder (2/8); Martha Wilson as Tipper Gore, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Green Folder (3/8); Tipper in PMI window 1994 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Green Folder (4/8) MW by Benita Abrams, undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Green Folder (5/8) Photos of MW, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Green Folder (6/8) MW as Tipper Gore, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Green Folder (7/8) Ms. Magazine, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Green Folder (8/8) Orchids, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Greg Bregere, 1987-1994 (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - Guerrilla Girls, 1993-1996 (Box 86, Folder 3-4)
    - Guggenheim app 2002 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Hamilton NAL Chapter XI, 1975, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Hemispheric Institute Anti-War Cabaret 7/17/03, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Heresies folder in Impractical folder, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - envelope from Heresies folder, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Holzer announcement, equitable 10/87 reject, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Ideas, 2001-2008 (Box 88, Folder 14-17)
    - Ideas-- Clothing Design [and graphology], Undated (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Impractical (1/2), 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Impractical (2/2), 1974, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Interregnum: in-between states, PSI #14, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Information Catalogue envelope, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Jarden/Wilson, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Jayne Wark article; Camera Obscura 2001 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Jayne Wark article on MW, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Just Say No to Nancy Bag, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Katy Kennedy, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Envelope to MW from Richard Kostelanetz, date illegible (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Languages, Chinese, undated (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Legal Documents (redact also includes letter from Callie) (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Letters to readers 3/91, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Leonardo Proposal August 2003 (1/3) (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Leonardo Proposal August 2003 (2/3) (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Leonardo Proposal 2003 (3/3) (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Literary Parallels [some restrictions], 1973, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Lolita Journal, Feb 96 and SAG membership, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - The making of a fishwife 1/18/98 (1/3), 1998 (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - The making of a fishwife 1/18/98 (2/3), 1998 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - The making of a fishwife 1/18/98 (3/3), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - The making of a fishwife program, January 18, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Malpede, John, Undated (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Membership Letter from Franklin Furnace, 1986 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - MW article in The Georgian, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - MW by Jide Ojo, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - MW in California trip, October 15-25 1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - MW at Maison Francaise [nuei] 12/7/99 (1/2), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - MW at Maison Francaise [nuei] 12/7/99 (2/2), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - MW in Japan, Febrary 26 - March 8 (1/2), 1996 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - MW in Japan, February 26 - March 8 (2/2), 1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Martha Wilson Press, 1979-1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - MW Videotape correspondence 8/94, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Martha Redy story announcement, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Marya Schwartzkopf, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - M/E/A/N/I/N/G 19/20, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Meta-Sondheim (1/3), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Meta-Sondheim (2/3), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Meta-Sondheim (3/3), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Money, c. 1983 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Montgomery 10/93, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - NEA Authorized Signature address book, Undated (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - National Review of Live Art, Feb. 2001 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Nep and Contact Sheet B Bush Jan '92, Photos by Paula Court, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - New Observations #95, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - NYFA 6/8/98, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - NYI Humanities, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - New Observations, May issue draft, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - New York Times review Personal and Political, Gloria Oct. 11, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - NYU student essays, 2009-2010 (Box 89, Folder 1-3)
    - NYU instructor evaluations, 2011 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - NYU Undergrad Drama 2002 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - NIPAF 96 Japan perf art festical catalogue, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Not in Our Name - New York Times, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Nova Scotia College of Art + Design, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - NYFA Fellowship and FYI 17:2 (FYI in Oversize), 2001 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Operation Iraqi Freedom and Separated at Birth research, 2003 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - The Organic Apple Campaign folder, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Parsons 2010, 2009-2010 (Box 88, Folder 11-12)
      - 4, undated; 700 Megabytes in one computer disc. (Box Shared Fales 007)
    - Parsons 2011 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Pending 1995, 1996, 1997 (1/3), 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Pending 1995, 1996, 1997 (2/3), 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Pending 1995, 1996, 1997 (3/3), 1995-1997 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Pending 11/98, (1/3), 1998 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Pending 11/98, (2/3), 1998 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Pending 11/98, (3/3), 1998 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Pending 1999-02, 1999-2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Pending 2000, (1/3) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Pending 2000, (2/3) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Pending 2000, (3/3) (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Pending 2001,02, 03, (1/2), 2001-2003 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Pending 2001, 02, 03, (2/2), 2001-2003 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Pending 2004, (1/3) (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Pending 2004, (2/3) (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Pending 2004, (3/3) (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Pending March 2008 and June 2009, 2007-2009 (Box 88, Folder 19-21)
    - PS. 2003-4, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Performance Art Tour, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      Includes materials from artists Barbara Bloom, Robert Longo, Larry Miller and Michael Smith.
    - Performance Art Tour: "Artful Doger" Robert Longo, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Performance Party, Martha's Bday, undated (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Performance Studies International 13, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Personal, nd [1980] (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Personal and Political exhibit at Guild Hall, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Personal and Political: The Woman's Art Movement, 1969-1973., 2002 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Photos, Grace Roselli, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Pix of Nancy Reagan & Tipper in PMI Window., 1984, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Plants, 1994-1995 (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Polaroid of Carel Balth Perception of the Line, undated (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Polaroid of Cubicle Book, undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Polaroid of Curt Barnes, Table of Contents, undated (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Polaroid of Gengui Numata (souvenir packet), undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Polaroid of Jerri Allyn, Love Novellas, undated (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Polaroid of K.U.N.S.T, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Polaroid of Laurie Anderson, Let X=X, undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Polaroid of Melody Summer, The Time is Now, undated (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Polaroid of Michael Corris, Typographic Samples, Pictures and Polemics, undated (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Polaroid of Sherri Levine, untitled, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Polaroid of Sol Lewitt, Brick Wall, undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Polaroid of Real Lush, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Polaroids of Un Coup de des, undated (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Polaroid of Yani Pecanins, Un viaje en Zeppelin, undated (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Polaroid of Yoko Ono Grapefruit, undated (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Practical -- Warranties etc. [1 of 2], 1974 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Practical -- Warranties etc. [2 of 2], 1974 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Project Studios One proposal, undated (Box Shared Fales 002, Folder 1-2)
    - William Pope, Maine College of Art, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - PR for the Wedding Deal, January 18, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Rawls & Son Wholesale Lumber, PO Box 58, Richardson, TX 75080 (1/2), 1987-1991 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Rawls & Son Wholesale Lumber, PO Box 58, Richardson, TX 75080 (2/2), Undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Republican Like Me - New York Times review 8/27/04, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Ruskin Envelope, Undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - School Baby (1/2), 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - School Baby (2/2), 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Slides of Early Work at York U. 1996 exhibition, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - School of Visual Art (SVA), 1978 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Secret Agency, Undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Soil and Health [Fdn], 1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Stationary, etc. - contact sheet of photos of MW, slide of open book, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Stories, working notes, Undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Swinburne (three articles), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Teaching Job -- Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Teaching Job -- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Teaching Job -- Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Television, 1991-1996 (Box 86, Folder 8-9)
    - Texts, Undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - THOTF calendar and Franklin Furnace stuff, 1999-2000 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Tipper Gore's Advice for the 90's, published in Japan catalog, negative, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Tipper Gore by Benita Abrams, Undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Tipper is Simon Says 2/18/98, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Tipper Gore research (1/2), 1992-2000 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Tipper Gore research (2/2), 1993-2000 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - TNYT Style 7/11/04, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - UK, 1994-1995 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Untitled Correspondence (1/4), 1992, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Untitled Correspondence (2/4), 1993, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Untitled Correspondence (3/4), 1994, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Untitled Correspondence (4/4), 1995 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Vince in the Village Voice 7/23/03, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Videostory, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Wedding PR in Village Voice, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - West Side Story Program, Undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Wilmington, includes 50 ft. Super 8mm Film Reel, 1969, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Words & Works, A-B, 1970, 1972, 1974, 1975, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Words & Works, C-F, 1973, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Words & Works, GHI, 1969, 1970, 1974-1977 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Words & Works, JKL, 1970, 1974, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Words & Works, MNOP, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Words & Works, QRSTU (1/2), 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Words & Works, QRSTU (2/2), 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Words & Works, VWXYZ, 1971, 1972, 1974-75 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Subseries B: Future of the Book project
    - Abstract (FOTB/BOTF), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - American Bible Society, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Ralph Appelbaum, 1979-1986 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Arian, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Art Forum, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Walter Bareiss, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Roland Barthes, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Baum, Timothy, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Berglund, Richard, Special Programs - IBM, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Braziller, George, Braziller, Inc., 1984 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Braziller, George, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Brieant, Virginia W. Contributions to the Arts, Warner Communications, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - (Kirkland, Isabella) John Brockman, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Jean, Shaker Seed House, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Bibliography, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Wm. Blake, The Book of Job (color xerox), undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Budgets, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Budget (FOTB/BOTF), undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Captions, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Center for the Book - Library of Congress, ca. 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Center for the Book - Interactive Microchip, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Center for Book Arts, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Champion International Corp., 1984 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Codex, undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Cohen, Arthur and Elaine, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Cohen, Mrs. Julius H., 1984 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Cohn, Theodore, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Benjamin Compaine, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Computer Masters, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Contracts and Lecturer Carr, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Corporation/ Foundation letters, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - CUNY, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Curator/Archivists/Consultants Resumes, undated (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Coleman, A.D., 1984 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - John M. Crawford Jr. Collection, Undated (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - William J. Dane Newark Public Lib., 1985 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Description (FOTB / BOTF), Undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Design Arts list of items, Undated (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Dorfman, Ariel, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Martha Driver, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Mindy Dubansky, Met Museum, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Eisenstein, Elizabeth, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Quentin Fiore, 1984-1996 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Vilem Flusser, Undated (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Freehlig, Stanley - Arts Club of Chicago, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Gary Frost (Chicago) info on bindings and conservation, Undated (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - FOTB 1986 exhibition checklist, 1985-1986 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - The Future of the Book folder, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - Getty Mus., 1984 (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Gilman Book, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - Giroux, Robert - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Godine, David - Godine Press, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - Gossett, Anne R. - SITES, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - Grolier Club, 1984-1986 (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - The Grolier Club (Robert Graff Preface), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - Harrison Roman, Gail, Undated (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - Highgate Art Trust, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - Hightower, Caroline - AIGA, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Matt Hogan, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Hoyem, Andrew, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Illustrations, Undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Incunabula, c. 1984 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition Installation, Undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - E. Powis Jones, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Kaplan, Jeremiah - MacMillan Publishing Co. Inc., 1984 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Kaplan, Margaret - Harry N. Abrams Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Kay, Alan C., 1984 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Kerr, William T. - NY Times, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Kiesler, Lillian, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Kucklick, Bette, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Lancaster, Dr. F.W., University of IL, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Law, Alma, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Learsy, Ray, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Lecture - FOTB, Undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Lee, Dr. Sherman, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Letters - Dear Artist (originals), 1984 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Letters - Introductory, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Letters - Support, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Liss, Amy, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Litewka, Albert, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Logan, David and Reva, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Lyons, Nathan - Visual Studies Workshop, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - McCorison, Marcus - American Antiquarian Society, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Malbin, Lydia, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Marinetti, Luce, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Messerli, Douglas - Sun and Moon Press, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Morgan Library, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Moyer, Jennifer - Coordinating Council of Lit'ry Mags, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Nadin, Peter, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Naef, Weston, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - NEA, Design Arts, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - NEH grant, submitted 10/31/83, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - NEH - Raided NEH proposal, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - NEH - revised proposals, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Nelson, Craig D. - Harper and Row, Publishers, Inc., 1984 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - New York Council for the Humanities, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - New York Institute for the Humanities, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - New York Public Library, 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - New York Public Library - Censorship: 500 Years of Conflict, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Newspaper information, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Notecards, Undated (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Notes file #1, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Notes - SH notes (FOTB notes), 1984 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Notes - Martha Wilson notes, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Object list, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Ogust, Richard, Undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Outlines, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Pending - Eliz Scarlatos Time-line, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Pending - Future Biz, Undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Periodicals, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Philipson, Morris - University of Chicago Press, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Princeton University French Dept. - Robert Danton and Natalie Zeman-Davis, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Publications, Undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - R.R. Bowker Co., 1984 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Reed, Peter, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Research notes and Reference books, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Ripley, Joan - Chappaqua Book Shop, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Rosenthal, Robert - Regenstein Library, University of Chicago, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Sackner, Ruth and Marvin, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Schwartz, Dieter, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Sparks, Esther - The Art Institute of Chicago, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Sponsorship - Franklin Furnace and The Grolier Club, 1983-1984 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Station #10, Independent Publishing, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Stein, Donna, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Stewart Rowling Mott Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Stoddard, Robert E. - Houghton Library, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Survey - ML, Undated (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Survey sent by Reese Williams, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Table of Contents, Undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Tannenbaum, Barbara - Oberlin College, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Tanselle, Thomas, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Tanselle, Thomas G. - J.S. Guggenheim Foundation, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Toffler, Alvin, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Toole, Barbara, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Tuchman, Gaye - Stanford Univ. Feminist Stds. Prog., 1984 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Turnbull, William - North Point Press, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Ungerliter, Joy - Hebrew Micrography, Undated (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - University of California, San Diego, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Untitled folder, Undated (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Untitled folder, 1981-1984 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Untitled folder, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - USIA - Jerry Prillaman, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Watson, Jeannette - Brooks and Co. / Darcy Foundation, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Wells, Jim - Newberry Library, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Weiss, Ted (Congressman), 1984 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Wilentz, Ted, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Wolf, Daniel - Daniel Wolf Gallery, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Wolfe, Louis - Bantam Books Inc., 1984 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Wool, Ira, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - The Word - station, Undated (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Wrolstad, Dr. Merald - Visible Language, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Year-end Appeal Letter 12/1/85, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - Zavrian, Suzanne, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - Zwicker, Tony, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 51)